[
    {
        "year": 2022,
        "question_number": 1,
        "question_text": "Kevin: Hi friends! What are you doing tonight? Would you like to go to the rock concert? Read the responses below. Who refuses Kevin's invitation with NO excuse?",
        "option_a": "I love rock music, but I can't join you tonight.",
        "option_b": "That would be great, but my cousin is coming.",
        "option_c": "I'd love to come, but I can't. I have to study.",
        "option_d": "It sounds awesome, but I have other plans.",
        "correct_option": "A",
        "topic": "Friendship"
    },
    {
        "year": 2022,
        "question_number": 2,
        "question_text": "Susan asks her friends how to prepare a tomato sauce. Below, you see her friends' responses. Ted: I don't know how to cook. So, I can't help you. Dylan: I will share my favorite recipe with you. I think you will like it. Nelly: Ask Pete, he knows how to make a tomato sauce. Pete: Chop the tomatoes and fry them in a pan. According to the responses above, who says something about the process of making a tomato sauce?",
        "option_a": "Ted",
        "option_b": "Dylan",
        "option_c": "Nelly",
        "option_d": "Pete",
        "correct_option": "D",
        "topic": "In The Kitchen"
    },
    {
        "year": 2022,
        "question_number": 3,
        "question_text": "Jess, Mark, Steve and Ann gave the following answers to their teacher's question. Jess : I practice my English. Mark : I read the news on different websites. Steve : I play online games. Ann : I do shopping. Which of the following is the teacher's question?",
        "option_a": "How do you connect to the Internet?",
        "option_b": "What is your favorite online game?",
        "option_c": "What do you usually do on the Internet?",
        "option_d": "How much time do you spend online after school?",
        "correct_option": "C",
        "topic": "The Internet"
    },
    {
        "year": 2022,
        "question_number": 4,
        "question_text": "Dear Jane, Thanks for your invitation. It would be great to come to your party tonight and see our high school friends, but I am going to Istanbul this evening. Bye, Lisa. According to the information above, why did Lisa write this email? To - - - -.",
        "option_a": "organize a party",
        "option_b": "refuse Jane's invitation",
        "option_c": "invite Jane to Istanbul",
        "option_d": "give information about the party",
        "correct_option": "B",
        "topic": "Friendship"
    },
    {
        "year": 2022,
        "question_number": 5,
        "question_text": "Jessica invites her friends to her sister's birthday party on Sunday evening. Below, you see her friends' responses to Jessica's invitation. Betty: Thanks, but my parents and I are going to a concert at 8 p.m. on Sunday. Carol: That sounds good but I have to study for my English exam with my project partners. Linda: Thank you for inviting me. I will come to the party with my cousins. Sally: That would be really great. I like parties and I'll be there with my family. Who refuses the invitation because she has a plan with her family?",
        "option_a": "Betty",
        "option_b": "Carol",
        "option_c": "Linda",
        "option_d": "Sally",
        "correct_option": "A",
        "topic": "Friendship"
    },
    {
        "year": 2022,
        "question_number": 6,
        "question_text": "Below, you see some parts of four different phone conversations. I - Nora : Hello, this is Nora calling. May I speak to Jack? Jack : Hello, Nora. This is Jack. What's up? II - Anna : I have a message for Mr. Smith. Kate : Alright, I'm ready to take your message. III - Jim : Could you tell him to call me back? Tom : Sorry, can you repeat it, please? I didn't hear you well. IV - Joe : Thanks, see you later. Max : OK, talk to you soon, take care. Which two people finish their phone conversation?",
        "option_a": "Nora - Jack",
        "option_b": "Anna - Kate",
        "option_c": "Jim - Tom",
        "option_d": "Joe - Max",
        "correct_option": "D",
        "topic": "On The Phone"
    },
    {
        "year": 2022,
        "question_number": 7,
        "question_text": "Mr. Johnson : Hello! This is Mr. Johnson calling. May I speak to Mr. Potter, please? Secretary : Hello, Mr. Johnson. - - - -. Would you like to leave a message for him? Mr. Johnson : No, thank you. I'll call again later. Secretary : All right, sir. Have a nice day. Which of the following does NOT complete the conversation above?",
        "option_a": "I can't put you through to him now, he has gone out",
        "option_b": "I will get him now, hold on please",
        "option_c": "He is not available at the moment",
        "option_d": "He is talking to a customer at the moment",
        "correct_option": "B",
        "topic": "On The Phone"
    },
    {
        "year": 2022,
        "question_number": 8,
        "question_text": "Rules for Creating a Password - I. Use three letters and three numbers in your password. II. Don't use your name in your password. Mike, Nancy, Robert and Dan have created the following passwords for their accounts. Mike's Password : 121234, Nancy's Password : nc2626, Robert's Password : tmr714, Dan's Password : Dan362. Who created a password according to the rules above?",
        "option_a": "Mike",
        "option_b": "Nancy",
        "option_c": "Robert",
        "option_d": "Dan",
        "correct_option": "C",
        "topic": "The Internet"
    },
    {
        "year": 2022,
        "question_number": 9,
        "question_text": "Read the conversation below. Diana : Let's eat pizza. There is a new pizza restaurant on Main Street. Melissa : Are you sure? I don't like their pizza. Sarah : Why don't we make it at home? It's the best thing I can cook. Maria : Yes, it is really easy. That's what I bake on Saturdays. I will help you. According to the conversation above, which two people state that they know how to make pizza?",
        "option_a": "Sarah and Maria",
        "option_b": "Melissa and Sarah",
        "option_c": "Maria and Diana",
        "option_d": "Diana and Melissa",
        "correct_option": "A",
        "topic": "In The Kitchen"
    },
    {
        "year": 2022,
        "question_number": 10,
        "question_text": "Read the conversation below. Jenny : Hi, Carla. Alice and I are going to watch a movie in my house tomorrow. Would you like to join us? Carla : Oh, I have to study for my exam but I can't say no to your invitation. Could you give me your address, please? Jenny : Alice can pick you up. She knows the address. Carla : That would be great. According to the conversation above, which of the following is correct?",
        "option_a": "Alice doesn't know Jenny's address but Carla knows it.",
        "option_b": "Carla and Jenny will go to Alice's house.",
        "option_c": "Alice, Carla and Jenny will watch the movie together.",
        "option_d": "Jenny doesn't want to study for the exam with Carla.",
        "correct_option": "C",
        "topic": "Friendship"
    }
]
